[
    {
        "Question":"1.  Which is the best Dog breed for hunting?",
        "Options": ["Begal", "Spaniel", "Blood Hound"],
        "Answer":"Spaniel"
    },
    {
        "Question":"2.  Which is the most popular breed of dog in the UK?",
        "Options": ["German Shepherd", "Labrador", "Beagle"],
        "Answer":"Beagle"
    },
    {
        "Question":"3.  Why is the poodle so ugly?",
        "Options": ["They look stupid", "They are stuck-up", "Both"],
        "Answer":"Both"
    },
    {
        "Question":"4.  Which dog breed is the rarest?",
        "Options": ["Azawakh", "Lunehund", "Otterhound"],
        "Answer":"Lunehund"
    },
    {
        "Question":"5.  Which breed was the first ever dog?",
        "Options": ["Mid-Vurshaan", "Golha-Dov", "Bonn-Oberkassel"],
        "Answer":"Bonn-Oberkassel"
    },
    {
        "Question":"6.  Which is the smartest dog (not bias)",
        "Options": ["Pitbull", "Border Collie", "Spaniel"],
        "Answer":"Spaniel"
    },
    {
        "Question":"7.  Which is the cutest dog?",
        "Options": ["Jack Russel", "Dalmation", "Spaniel"],
        "Answer":"Dalmation"
    },
    {
        "Question":"8.  What is the least popular dog?",
        "Options": ["Cinook", "Foxhound", "Cesky Terrier"],
        "Answer":"Cesky Terrier"
    },
    {
        "Question":"9.  Why are dogs so loyal?",
        "Options": ["We smelt nice", "We are stronger", "We had food"],
        "Answer":"We had food"
    },
    {
        "Question":"10.  What is the average dog IQ",
        "Options": ["78", "100", "69"],
        "Answer":"100"
    },
    {
        "Question":"11.  Which is the best Spaniel variant?",
        "Options": ["Cocker", "Clumber", "Springer"],
        "Answer":"Cocker"
    }
]